Tufts New England Medical Center Planning Office Records UA014
Digital Collections and Archives, Tufts University
- Loose photographs, 1870 -- 1976; 1960 -- 1970; UA014.001; 1.2 Linear Feet; 470 Digital Object(s)
  - Fallout shelter in the South Cove area, 1967; UA014.001.DO.03051; Unknown (Box data_value_missing_f192f5c8820b07dbf78c0820404a09b6)
    Consists of 3 photos taped together.
  - View of a building in the South Cove area, 1967-12; UA014.001.DO.03052; Unknown (Box data_value_missing_f192f5c8820b07dbf78c0820404a09b6)
    Consists of 2 photos taped together.
  - View of the Music Hall Theater at the corner of Dillaway and Dore Streets, 1967-12; UA014.001.DO.03053; Unknown (Box data_value_missing_f192f5c8820b07dbf78c0820404a09b6)
  - East elevator of the Music Hall Theater from Dillaway Street, 1967; UA014.001.DO.03054; Unknown (Box data_value_missing_f192f5c8820b07dbf78c0820404a09b6)
    Buildings; Elevators; Tufts New England Medical Center, records; Music Hall Theater
  - Ziskind Research Laboratories and adjacent parking lot, 1967; UA014.001.DO.03055; Unknown (Box data_value_missing_f192f5c8820b07dbf78c0820404a09b6)
    Consists of 3 photos taped together; photo is damaged.
    Buildings; Laboratories; Parking lots; Tufts New England Medical Center, records; Ziskind Research Laboratories
  - Ziskind Research Laboratories with an officer standing in front of the doorway, 1967; UA014.001.DO.03056; Unknown (Box data_value_missing_f192f5c8820b07dbf78c0820404a09b6)
    Consists of 2 photos taped together; photo is damaged.
  - Buildings in the South Cove area, 1967; UA014.001.DO.03057; Unknown (Box data_value_missing_f192f5c8820b07dbf78c0820404a09b6)
    .5 x 1 in. photo printed on 8 x 10 in. paper
  - Building in the South Cove area, 1967; UA014.001.DO.03058; Unknown (Box data_value_missing_f192f5c8820b07dbf78c0820404a09b6)
  - Boston Dispensary in the South Cove area, 1967; UA014.001.DO.03059; Unknown (Box data_value_missing_f192f5c8820b07dbf78c0820404a09b6)
  - Street and surrounding buildings in the South Cove area, 1967; UA014.001.DO.03060; Unknown (Box data_value_missing_f192f5c8820b07dbf78c0820404a09b6)
  - Building in the South Cove area, 1967; UA014.001.DO.03061; Unknown (Box data_value_missing_f192f5c8820b07dbf78c0820404a09b6)
  - Building in the South Cove area, 1967; UA014.001.DO.03062; Unknown (Box data_value_missing_f192f5c8820b07dbf78c0820404a09b6)
  - Street and surrounding buildings in the South Cove area, 1967; UA014.001.DO.03063; Unknown (Box data_value_missing_f192f5c8820b07dbf78c0820404a09b6)
  - Building in the South Cove area with a parking lot in the foreground, 1967; UA014.001.DO.03064; Unknown (Box data_value_missing_f192f5c8820b07dbf78c0820404a09b6)
  - Buildings in the South Cove area, one of which houses the Allied Marking Device Co. and the Macy Drug Store, 1967; UA014.001.DO.03065; Unknown (Box data_value_missing_f192f5c8820b07dbf78c0820404a09b6)
    Buildings; Tufts New England Medical Center, records; Allied Marking Device Co.; Macy Drug Store
  - Buildings along a street in the South Cove area, 1967; UA014.001.DO.03066; Unknown (Box data_value_missing_f192f5c8820b07dbf78c0820404a09b6)
  - Buildings along a street in the South Cove area, 1967; UA014.001.DO.03067; Unknown (Box data_value_missing_f192f5c8820b07dbf78c0820404a09b6)
  - Buildings in the South Cove area, 1967; UA014.001.DO.03068; Unknown (Box data_value_missing_f192f5c8820b07dbf78c0820404a09b6)
  - Buildings and street in the South Cove area, 1967; UA014.001.DO.03069; Unknown (Box data_value_missing_f192f5c8820b07dbf78c0820404a09b6)
  - A building and lot in the South Cove area, 1967; UA014.001.DO.03070; Unknown (Box data_value_missing_f192f5c8820b07dbf78c0820404a09b6)
  - A rubble-filled lot with buildings in the background, 1967; UA014.001.DO.03071; Unknown (Box data_value_missing_f192f5c8820b07dbf78c0820404a09b6)
  - Rubble-filled lot with buildings in the background, 1967; UA014.001.DO.03072; Unknown (Box data_value_missing_f192f5c8820b07dbf78c0820404a09b6)
  - Building in the South Cove area, 1967; UA014.001.DO.03073; Unknown (Box data_value_missing_f192f5c8820b07dbf78c0820404a09b6)
  - Rubble-filled lot with building in the background, 1967; UA014.001.DO.03074; Unknown (Box data_value_missing_f192f5c8820b07dbf78c0820404a09b6)
  - Artist's rendering of the entrance to the proposed Tufts-New England Medical Center, 1969; UA014.001.DO.03075; Unknown (Box data_value_missing_f192f5c8820b07dbf78c0820404a09b6)
    Drawing includes the retail shopping center with apartments above, outpatient clinics, upper-level bridges, subway exit and pedestrian entrance to the medical center, and upper level of the research building.
    Buildings; Tufts New England Medical Center, records; New England Medical Center
  - Model of the Tufts-New England Medical Center, 1969; UA014.001.DO.03076; Harvey, Robert D. (Box Shared 19)
  - Model of the Tufts-New England Medical Center, 1969; UA014.001.DO.03077; Karas, Phokion (Box Shared 19)
  - View of the Back Bay, 1967; UA014.001.DO.03078; Unknown (Box Shared 41)
    Color slide
    Views; Tufts New England Medical Center, records
  - Buildings along Fayette Street in the Bay Village, 1967; UA014.001.DO.03079; Unknown (Box Shared 41)
  - Doctors performing surgery, 1967; UA014.001.DO.03080; Unknown (Box Shared 42)
    Copy negative
    People; Surgeons; Tufts New England Medical Center, records; New England Medical Center
  - View of several windows along side the corner of a building in the South Cove area, 1967; UA014.001.DO.03081; Unknown (Box data_value_missing_f192f5c8820b07dbf78c0820404a09b6)
  - North on Shawmut Avenue, 1964; UA014.001.DO.03082; Unknown (Box data_value_missing_f192f5c8820b07dbf78c0820404a09b6)
  - East on Stuart Street with Tremont Street in the foreground, 1964; UA014.001.DO.03083; Unknown (Box data_value_missing_f192f5c8820b07dbf78c0820404a09b6)
  - Photo taken from halfway between Stuart Street and Hollis Street, 1964; UA014.001.DO.03084; Unknown (Box data_value_missing_f192f5c8820b07dbf78c0820404a09b6)
  - East on Stuart Street from Eliot Street, 1964; UA014.001.DO.03085; Unknown (Box data_value_missing_f192f5c8820b07dbf78c0820404a09b6)
  - West on Stuart Street with Washington Street intersecting at "Allied Marking", 1964; UA014.001.DO.03086; Unknown (Box data_value_missing_32ad063264334f9fe0c246c227e9f97e)
    Views; Buildings; Tufts New England Medical Center, records; Allied Marking Device Co.
  - North on Harrison Avenue, 1964; UA014.001.DO.03087; Unknown (Box data_value_missing_32ad063264334f9fe0c246c227e9f97e)
  - West on Stuart Street from the intersectoin at Stuart Street and Tremont Street, 1964; UA014.001.DO.03088; Unknown (Box data_value_missing_32ad063264334f9fe0c246c227e9f97e)
  - East on Harvard Street from Washington Street, 1964; UA014.001.DO.03089; Unknown (Box data_value_missing_32ad063264334f9fe0c246c227e9f97e)
  - Collage of photos depicting the Boston Children's Floating Hospital, 1894 -- 1970; UA014.001.DO.03090; Unknown (Box data_value_missing_32ad063264334f9fe0c246c227e9f97e)
    People; Hospitals; Models (representations); Tufts New England Medical Center, records; Boston Floating Hospital; New England Medical Center
  - Exterior of the Stearns Research Building at the Tufts Schools of Medicine and Dental Medicine, 1964; UA014.001.DO.03091; Boston Photo Company (Box data_value_missing_32ad063264334f9fe0c246c227e9f97e)
    Photo has been torn on the upper right-hand side.
    Buildings; Tufts New England Medical Center, records; Tufts School of Medicine; School of Dental Medicine; New England Medical Center
  - View of street and surrouding structures with the Stearns Research Building in the background, 1964; UA014.001.DO.03092; Harvey, Robert D. (Box data_value_missing_32ad063264334f9fe0c246c227e9f97e)
  - Scaffolding along the side of the Ziskind Research Laboratory, 1967; UA014.001.DO.03093; Lenscraft Photos, INC. (Box data_value_missing_32ad063264334f9fe0c246c227e9f97e)
  - South on Tremont Street with Stuart Street in the foreground, 1964; UA014.001.DO.03094; Harvey, Robert D. (Box data_value_missing_32ad063264334f9fe0c246c227e9f97e)
  - Stearns Research Building at the Tufts Schools of Medicine and Dental Medicine, 1964; UA014.001.DO.03095; Lenscraft Photos, INC. (Box data_value_missing_32ad063264334f9fe0c246c227e9f97e)
  - North on Shawmut Avenue, 1964; UA014.001.DO.03096; Harvey, Robert D. (Box data_value_missing_32ad063264334f9fe0c246c227e9f97e)
  - North on Harrison Avenue, 1964; UA014.001.DO.03097; Harvey, Robert D. (Box data_value_missing_32ad063264334f9fe0c246c227e9f97e)
  - New England Medical Center Hospital, 1950; UA014.001.DO.03098; Unknown (Box data_value_missing_32ad063264334f9fe0c246c227e9f97e)
    Photo is damaged.
    Buildings; Hospitals; Tufts New England Medical Center, records; Tufts School of Medicine; School of Dental Medicine; New England Medical Center
  - Intersection at Kneeland Street and possibly Washington or Tremont Streets, 1964; UA014.001.DO.03099; Harvey, Robert D. (Box data_value_missing_32ad063264334f9fe0c246c227e9f97e)
  - Two unidentified men walking on a sidewalk and street beside a building in the South Cove area, 1964; UA014.001.DO.03100; Unknown (Box data_value_missing_32ad063264334f9fe0c246c227e9f97e)
  - Truck parked along side a building in the South Cove area, 1967; UA014.001.DO.03101; Unknown (Box data_value_missing_32ad063264334f9fe0c246c227e9f97e)
  - Storefront of a building in the South Cove area, 1967; UA014.001.DO.03102; Unknown (Box data_value_missing_32ad063264334f9fe0c246c227e9f97e)
  - The Boston Floating Hospital's Jackson Memorial Building, 1935; UA014.001.DO.03103; Unknown (Box data_value_missing_32ad063264334f9fe0c246c227e9f97e)
    Buildings; Hospitals; Tufts New England Medical Center, records; Boston Floating Hospital; New England Medical Center
  - North on Shawmut Avenue or Tremont Street from Broadway St., 1964; UA014.001.DO.03104; Unknown (Box data_value_missing_32ad063264334f9fe0c246c227e9f97e)
    Title written on back of photo unclear of location: "Shawmut-Tremont North from Broadway"
  - South on Shawmut Avenue with Broadway in the foreground, 1964; UA014.001.DO.03105; Unknown (Box data_value_missing_32ad063264334f9fe0c246c227e9f97e)
  - North on Tremont Street with Broadway in foreground, 1964; UA014.001.DO.03106; Unknown (Box data_value_missing_f7a59bebc57b0ddc6de388e12e62cfb4)
  - West on Harvard Street, 1964; UA014.001.DO.03107; Unknown (Box data_value_missing_f7a59bebc57b0ddc6de388e12e62cfb4)
  - Nurses standing behind the Ziskind Laboratory, 1964; UA014.001.DO.03108; Lenscraft Photos, INC. (Box data_value_missing_f7a59bebc57b0ddc6de388e12e62cfb4)
    People; Buildings; Tufts New England Medical Center, records; Ziskind Research Laboratories
  - Unidentified building in the South Cove area, 1964; UA014.001.DO.03109; Unknown (Box data_value_missing_f7a59bebc57b0ddc6de388e12e62cfb4)
  - North on Harrison Avenue with Kneeland Street in the foreground, 1964; UA014.001.DO.03110; Unknown (Box data_value_missing_f7a59bebc57b0ddc6de388e12e62cfb4)
  - Unidentified building in the South Cove area, 1964; UA014.001.DO.03111; Unknown (Box data_value_missing_f7a59bebc57b0ddc6de388e12e62cfb4)
  - North facade of Posner Hall, 1964; UA014.001.DO.03112; Unknown (Box data_value_missing_f7a59bebc57b0ddc6de388e12e62cfb4)
    Buildings; Dormitories; Tufts New England Medical Center, records; Tufts School of Medicine; School of Dental Medicine; New England Medical Center
  - North on Tyler Street with Harvard Street in the foreground, 1964; UA014.001.DO.03113; Unknown (Box data_value_missing_f7a59bebc57b0ddc6de388e12e62cfb4)
  - North on Harrison Avenue near dormitory, 1964; UA014.001.DO.03114; Unknown (Box data_value_missing_f7a59bebc57b0ddc6de388e12e62cfb4)
    Dormitory is perhaps Posner Hall.
  - Buildings at the corner of Harvard Street and an unidentified street in the South Cove area, 1940; UA014.001.DO.03115; Unknown (Box data_value_missing_f7a59bebc57b0ddc6de388e12e62cfb4)
  - North on Harrison Street from in front of the Boston Dispensary, 1964; UA014.001.DO.03116; Unknown (Box data_value_missing_d89a03fc8351d427c827230e31640ebc)
    Views; Buildings; Tufts New England Medical Center, records; Boston Dispensary
  - East on Kneeland Street with Washington Street in the foreground, 1964; UA014.001.DO.03117; Unknown (Box data_value_missing_d89a03fc8351d427c827230e31640ebc)
  - West on Kneeland Street with Harrison Avenue in the foreground, 1964; UA014.001.DO.03118; Harvey, Robert D. (Box data_value_missing_d89a03fc8351d427c827230e31640ebc)
  - South on Washington Street with Stuart Street in the foreground, 1964; UA014.001.DO.03119; Unknown (Box data_value_missing_d89a03fc8351d427c827230e31640ebc)
  - West on Bennet Street from Harrison Avenue, 1964; UA014.001.DO.03120; Unknown (Box data_value_missing_d89a03fc8351d427c827230e31640ebc)
  - North on Tremont Street with Broadway Street in the foreground, 1964; UA014.001.DO.03121; Unknown (Box data_value_missing_d89a03fc8351d427c827230e31640ebc)
  - North on Washington Street from Oak Street, 1964; UA014.001.DO.03122; Unknown (Box data_value_missing_d89a03fc8351d427c827230e31640ebc)
  - North on Washington Street from the expressway bridge, 1964; UA014.001.DO.03123; Unknown (Box data_value_missing_d89a03fc8351d427c827230e31640ebc)
  - Don Bosco Technical High School, 1964; UA014.001.DO.03124; Unknown (Box data_value_missing_d89a03fc8351d427c827230e31640ebc)
    Photo consists of two 7 x 5 in. photos placed together.
    Buildings; Schools; Tufts New England Medical Center, records; Don Bosco Technical High School
  - East on Oak Street from Harrison Avenue, 1964; UA014.001.DO.03125; Harvey, Robert D. (Box data_value_missing_d89a03fc8351d427c827230e31640ebc)
  - West on Oak Street from Hudson Street, 1964; UA014.001.DO.03126; Unknown (Box data_value_missing_d89a03fc8351d427c827230e31640ebc)
  - West on Harvard Street with Harrison Avenue in the foreground, 1964; UA014.001.DO.03127; Harvey, Robert D. (Box data_value_missing_d89a03fc8351d427c827230e31640ebc)
  - East on Harvard Street with Harrison Avenue in foreground, 1964; UA014.001.DO.03128; Harvey, Robert D. (Box data_value_missing_d89a03fc8351d427c827230e31640ebc)
  - Intersection at Oak and Ash Streets, 1964; UA014.001.DO.03129; Unknown (Box data_value_missing_d89a03fc8351d427c827230e31640ebc)
  - East on Oak Street with Tyler Street in the background, 1964; UA014.001.DO.03130; Harvey, Robert D. (Box data_value_missing_d89a03fc8351d427c827230e31640ebc)
  - South Shawmut Avenue from Tremont Street, 1964; UA014.001.DO.03131; Harvey, Robert D. (Box data_value_missing_d89a03fc8351d427c827230e31640ebc)
  - Tufts-New England Medical Center building, 1975-11; UA014.001.DO.03132; Unknown (Box Shared 41)
    Buildings; Hospitals; Tufts New England Medical Center, records; New England Medical Center; Tufts School of Medicine; School of Dental Medicine
  - Buildings in the South Cove area, 1975-11; UA014.001.DO.03133; Unknown (Box Shared 41)
  - South Cove playground area, 1968-10; UA014.001.DO.03134; Unknown (Box Shared 41)
  - View of the Prudential Building and the Back Bay area, 1975; UA014.001.DO.03135; Unknown (Box Shared 41)
  - Parade and festivities in the South Cove area, 1967-02; UA014.001.DO.03136; Unknown (Box Shared 41)
    Parades; Tufts New England Medical Center, records
  - Three unidentified men discussing a model of the New England Medical Center, 1969; UA014.001.DO.03137; Unknown (Box Shared 33)
    People; Models (representations); Tufts New England Medical Center, records; New England Medical Center
  - Children standing on a stoop outside of a home in the South Cove area, 1964; UA014.001.DO.03138; Unknown (Box Shared 33)
    People; Children; Houses; Tufts New England Medical Center, records
  - Children sitting on the stoop outside of a home in the South Cove area, 1964; UA014.001.DO.03139; Unknown (Box Shared 33)
  - Upper facade of a home in the South Cove area, 1964; UA014.001.DO.03140; Unknown (Box Shared 33)
    Buildings; Houses; Tufts New England Medical Center, records
  - Young boy sitting on the deck of the Boston Floating Hospital for Children and Infants, 1926; UA014.001.DO.03141; Unknown (Box Shared 43)
    People; Children; Hospitals; Tufts New England Medical Center, records; Boston Floating Hospital; New England Medical Center
  - Doctors at the Boston Floating Hospital, 1926; UA014.001.DO.03142; Unknown (Box Shared 43)
    People; Hospitals; Tufts New England Medical Center, records; Boston Floating Hospital; New England Medical Center
  - Child in a wheelchair receiving care at the Boston Floating Hospital, 1970; UA014.001.DO.03143; Unknown (Box Shared 43)
  - Young girl with a doll, 1970; UA014.001.DO.03144; Unknown (Box Shared 43)
  - Nurses at the Boston Floating Hospital, 1926; UA014.001.DO.03145; Unknown (Box Shared 43)
  - Artist's rendering of how children were cared for at the Boston Floating Hospital, 1900; UA014.001.DO.03146; Unknown (Box Shared 43)
    4.5 x 5.5 in copy negative and a 2 x 2 in. color slide.
  - Doctors and nurses at the "On Shore Department" of the Boston Floating Hospital, 1926; UA014.001.DO.03147; Unknown (Box Shared 43)
  - Sick children and their caretakers at the Boston Floating Hospital, 1900; UA014.001.DO.03148; Unknown (Box Shared 43)
  - Church and buildings along a road in the South Cove area, 1964; UA014.001.DO.03149; Unknown (Box Shared 33)
    Views; Buildings; Churches; Tufts New England Medical Center, records
  - Views of buildings and street in the South Cove area, 1964; UA014.001.DO.03150; Unknown (Box Shared 33)
    Photo contained in envelope with UI03151/03152.
  - Backyards and gardens in the area between buildings, 1964; UA014.001.DO.03151; Unknown (Box Shared 33)
    Photo contained in envelope with UI03150/03152.
  - Unidentified person walking on the sidewalk toward John S. Lufty Square, 1964; UA014.001.DO.03152; Unknown (Box Shared 33)
    Photo contained in envelope with UI03150/03151.
    Views; Buildings; People; Tufts New England Medical Center, records
  - City street in the South Cove area, 1964; UA014.001.DO.03153; Unknown (Box Shared 33)
    Photo contained in envelope with UI03154/03155.
  - View of a street near its intersection with Fayette Street, 1964; UA014.001.DO.03154; Unknown (Box Shared 33)
    Photo contained in envelope with UI03153/03155.
  - Area in or around South Cove, 1964; UA014.001.DO.03155; Unknown (Box Shared 33)
    Photo contained in envelope with UI03153/03154.
  - Cars parked along the street in the South Cove area, 1964; UA014.001.DO.03156; Unknown (Box Shared 33)
    Photo contained in envelope with UI03157/03158.
    Views; Buildings; Tufts New England Medical Center, records; Automobiles
  - Street located in the South Cove area, 1964; UA014.001.DO.03157; Unknown (Box Shared 33)
    Photo contained in envelope with UI03156/03158.
  - Building and cars parked along a street in the South Cove area, 1964; UA014.001.DO.03158; Unknown (Box Shared 33)
    Photo contained in envelope with UI03156/03157.
  - Area near South Cove, 1964; UA014.001.DO.03159; Unknown (Box Shared 33)
    Photo contained in envelope with UI03160/03161.
  - Buildings and cars along a street in the South Cove area, 1964; UA014.001.DO.03160; Unknown (Box Shared 33)
    Photo contained in envelope with UI03159/03161.
  - Houses and cars in the South Cove area, 1964; UA014.001.DO.03161; Unknown (Box Shared 33)
    Photo contained in envelope with UI03159/03160.
    Views; Buildings; Houses; Tufts New England Medical Center, records; Automobiles
  - Cranes working at a demolition site in the South Cove area, 1968-10; UA014.001.DO.03162; Unknown (Box Shared 33)
    Views; Buildings; Tufts New England Medical Center, records; Demolition sites
  - Unidentified building along a body of water, 1962-08; UA014.001.DO.03163; Unknown (Box Shared 33)
  - Buildings along the street in the South Cove area, 1964; UA014.001.DO.03164; Unknown (Box Shared 33)
    "BW Bay Village and Medical Center area shots" written on envelope containing negatives and pictures.
  - View of street in the South Cove area, 1964; UA014.001.DO.03165; Unknown (Box Shared 33)
    "BW Bay Village and Medical Center area shots" written on the envelope containing negatives and pictures.
  - View of a home in the South Cove area, 1964; UA014.001.DO.03166; Unknown (Box Shared 33)
    Views; Buildings; Houses; Tufts New England Medical Center, records
  - View of homes in the South Cove area, 1964; UA014.001.DO.03167; Unknown (Box Shared 33)
  - View of area in South Cove, 1964; UA014.001.DO.03168; Unknown (Box Shared 33)
  - View of area in South Cove, 1964; UA014.001.DO.03169; Unknown (Box Shared 33)
  - Buildings surrounding the corner of Ash Street in the South Cove area, 1964; UA014.001.DO.03170; Unknown (Box Shared 33)
  - Buildings surrounding a parking lot in the South Cove area, 1964; UA014.001.DO.03171; Unknown (Box Shared 33)
  - View of an area in South Cove, 1964; UA014.001.DO.03172; Unknown (Box Shared 33)
  - View of buildings and train tracks in the South Cove area, 1964; UA014.001.DO.03173; Unknown (Box Shared 33)
  - A car parked in the South Cove area with a parking lot and buildings in the background, 1964; UA014.001.DO.03174; Unknown (Box Shared 33)
    Views; Buildings; Tufts New England Medical Center, records; Automobiles; Parking lots
  - The sidewalk and side wall of The Boston Floating Hospital, 1964; UA014.001.DO.03175; Unknown (Box Shared 33)
    Views; Buildings; Hospitals; Tufts New England Medical Center, records; Boston Floating Hospital
  - View of Tremont Street and Shawmut Avenue West, 1870; UA014.001.DO.03176; Unknown (Box Shared 43)
  - The Music Hall located at the corner of Hollis Street and Dillaway Street, 1967; UA014.001.DO.03178; Unknown (Box Shared 33)
    Photo consists of four separate photos taped together.
    Buildings; Tufts New England Medical Center, records; Music Hall Theater
  - A hotel, homes, and other buildings in the South Cove area, 1975-11; UA014.001.DO.03179; Unknown (Box Shared 41)
    Buildings; Tufts New England Medical Center, records; Houses; Hotels
  - The Howard Johnson's Motor Lodge and other buildings in the South Cove area, 1975-11; UA014.001.DO.03180; Unknown (Box Shared 41)
    Buildings; Hotels; Tufts New England Medical Center, records
  - The Howard Johnson's Motor Lodge in the South Cove area, 1976-11; UA014.001.DO.03181; Unknown (Box Shared 41)
  - Homes and surrounding buildings at the corner of Church Street, 1975-11; UA014.001.DO.03182; Unknown (Box Shared 41)
  - A park in the South Cove area, 1969-11; UA014.001.DO.03183; Unknown (Box Shared 41)
  - Two young girls playing in a South Cove park, 1969-11; UA014.001.DO.03184; Unknown (Box Shared 41)
    Views; Tufts New England Medical Center, records; Parks (grounds)
  - Aerial view of the South Cove area, 1970-06; UA014.001.DO.03185; Unknown (Box Shared 41)
  - Aerial view of the South Cove area, 1970-06; UA014.001.DO.03186; Unknown (Box Shared 41)
  - Aerial view of the South Cove area, 1970-06; UA014.001.DO.03187; Unknown (Box Shared 41)
  - Proposed boating and recreation area, 1966-03; UA014.001.DO.03188; Unknown (Box Shared 41)
    Black and white slide
    Views; Drawings; Tufts New England Medical Center, records
  - Proposed changes to Cambridge Street from the Charles River to New City Hill, 1966-03; UA014.001.DO.03189; Unknown (Box Shared 41)
  - Proposed high rise housing in the waterfront area, 1966-03; UA014.001.DO.03190; Unknown (Box Shared 41)
  - Proposed BRA General Plan, 1960-1975, 1966-03; UA014.001.DO.03191; Unknown (Box Shared 41)
    Black and white slide; 1st drawing: Proposed Charlestown Elementary School; 2nd drawing: Small recreation space; 3rd drawing: Pedestrian area
    Views; Buildings; Schools; Drawings; Tufts New England Medical Center, records; Bogner & Richard Architects